A Guide to the Pete Calos Photograph Collection, 1977-2005
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Petersburg Churches., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - W. Washington Street - sanctuary and alter - (Othertype 1:204)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - sanctuary and balcony - (Othertype 1:205)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:206)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - detail of altar and cross - (Othertype 1:207)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - Behold, I stand at the door - stained glass - (Othertype 1:208)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - interior showing stained glass - (Othertype 1:209)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - stained glass of Good Sheppard - (Othertype 1:210)
  - Harvest International Church - (Othertype 1:211)
  - Ekklesia - (Othertype 1:212)
  - Ekklesia - (Othertype 1:213)
  - Glory of God Ministry - (Othertype 1:214)
  - Baptist Temple Church - Plum and Hurt Streets - (Othertype 1:215)
  - Joy Faith - 615 High Street - (Othertype 1:216)
  - Oak St. AME Zion, and St. Paul's Episcopal Church - (Othertype 1:217)
  - Trinity Methodist - 215 S. Sycamore Street - (Othertype 1:218)
  - Trinity Methodist - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:219)
  - Trinity Methodist Church - altar (Othertype 1:220)
  - Trinity Methodist Church - railing and shadows - (Othertype 1:221)
  - First Baptist Church - exterior - (Othertype 1:222)
  - First Baptist Church - exterior - (Othertype 1:223)
  - First Baptist Church - stained glass and church plaque (Othertype 1:224)
  - First Baptist Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:225)
  - First Baptist Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:226)
  - First Baptist Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:227)
  - Zion Baptist Church - 225 Byrne Street - (Othertype 1:228)
  - Gilford Baptist Church - 209 Perry Street - (Othertype 1:229)
  - Gilford Baptist Church - 209 Perry Street - (Othertype 1:230)
  - House of Restoration - 210 S. Market Street - (Othertype 1:231)
  - House of Restoration - 210 S. Market Street - (Othertype 1:232)
  - House of Restoration - 210 S. Market Street- front gate and railing - (Othertype 1:233)
  - Trinity Missionary Baptist - 233 Halifax Street - (Othertype 1:234)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - (Othertype 1:235)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - altar and stained glass - (Othertype 1:236)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - altar - (Othertype 1:237)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:238)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - stained glass - (Othertype 1:239)
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal - Halifax Street - (Othertype 1:240)
  - Tabernacle Baptist Church - 418 Halifax Street - (Othertype 1:241)
  - Tabernacle Baptist Church - 418 Halifax Street - (Othertype 1:242)
  - Blandford Church - entry and tombstones - (Othertype 1:243)
  - Blandford Church - brickwork and glazed headers - (Othertype 1:244)
  - Blandford Church - St. Andrew - stained glass - (Othertype 1:245)
  - Blandford Church - St. Luke - stained glass - (Othertype 1:246)
  - Blandford Church - St. Mathew - stained glass - (Othertype 1:247)
  - Blandford Church - Arkansas - stained glass - (Othertype 1:248)
  - Blandford Church - St. Thomas, Georgia - stained glass - (Othertype 1:249)
  - Blandford Church - St. Philip, Tennessee - stained glass - (Othertype 1:250)
  - Blandford Church - St. James the Less, Mississippi - stained glass - (Othertype 1:251)
  - Blandford Church - St. Peter, Missouri - stained glass - (Othertype 1:252)
  - Blandford Church - St. John, Virginia - stained glass - (Othertype 1:253)
  - Blandford Church - St. Paul, Louisianna - stained glass - (Othertype 1:254)
  - Blandford Church - St. Bartholomew, North Carolina - stained glass - (Othertype 1:255)
  - Blandford Church - St. Mark, South Carolina - stained glass - (Othertype 1:256)
  - Blandford Church - stained glass Tiffany Cross - (Othertype 1:257)
  - Blandford Church - Assumption, Confederate Ladies Memorial - stained glass - (Othertype 1:258)
  - Blandford Church - cemetery - (Othertype 1:259)
  - Blandford Church - Stone Gate and cemetery - (Othertype 1:260)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church (Othertype 1:261)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church (Othertype 1:262)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church (Othertype 1:263)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:264)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - Tiffany stained glass - (Othertype 1:265)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - detail of Tiffany stained glass - (Othertype 1:266)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - Jennie Short - stained glass - (Othertype 1:267)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - E.C. Bulifant - stained glass - (Othertype 1:268)
  - Christ and Grace Episcopal Church - Julia Zimmer - stained glass - (Othertype 1:269)
  - Birith Achim - N. Market Street - formerly a Salvation Army, demolished December 2003 - (Othertype 1:270)
  - Birith Achim - N. Market Street - stained glass - (Othertype 1:271)
  - Birith Achim - N. Market Street - stained glass - (Othertype 1:272)
  - Birith Achim - N. Market Street - menorah - (Othertype 1:273)
  - Birith Achim - N. Market Street - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:274)
  - Emmanuel Baptist Church - (Othertype 1:275)
  - Pocahontas Chapel, Pocahontas Island - 143 Whitten Street - (Othertype 1:276)
  - Pocahontas Island Slave Museum - (Othertype 1:277)
- Series IV: Historic Churches., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  Richmond Historic Churches documents significant churches, predominately in the downtown Richmond area taken (unless specifically noted) during 2002. Calos documents the exterior, and when access was allowed - recorded the sanctuary, altar, and noteworthy architectural details.
  - St. John's Episcopal Church - 2401 E. Broad (Othertype 1:278)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - front - (Othertype 1:279)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - rear - (Othertype 1:280)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - interior - (Othertype 1:281)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - interior pews - (Othertype 1:282)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - interior stairs - (Othertype 1:283)
  - Monumental Episcopal Church - 1224 E. Broad Street - aerial view - (Othertype 1:283)
  - Centenary Methodist Church - 411 E. Grace Street - pipe organ - (Othertype 1:284)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - (Othertype 1:285)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - (Othertype 1:286)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - interior - (Othertype 1:287)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - during service - (Othertype 1:288)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - organ pipes - (Othertype 1:289)
  - S t. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Annunciation - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:290)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Moses Leaving the House of the Pharoahs - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:291)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Christ Healing the Sick - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:292)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - The Ascension - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:293)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Moses presenting the Ten Commandments - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:294)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Jesus Among the Elders Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:295)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Raising the Widow's son - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:296)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Tompkins Window - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:297)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - Young Crusader - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:298)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - The Angel of Hope - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:299)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - The Virtue of Charity - Tiffany glass - (Othertype 1:300)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - 815 E. Grace - The Angels of Goodness and Mercy - Tiffany stained glass - (Othertype 1:301)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - 5 North Fifth Street - (Othertype 1:302)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - 5 North Fifth Street - view from altar to pipe organ - (Othertype 1:303)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - 5 North Fifth Street - sanctuary and side transept - (Othertype 1:304)
  - Leigh Street Baptist Church - 517 N. 25th Street - altar and pipe organ - (Othertype 1:305)
  - Leigh Street Baptist Church - 517 N. 25th Street - altar and pipe organ - (Othertype 1:306)
  - New Light Baptist (old Trinity Methodist) - 2000 E. Broad Street - (Othertype 1:307)
  - New Light Baptist (old Trinity Methodist) - 2000 E. Broad Street - (Othertype 1:308)
  - New Light Baptist (old Trinity Methodist) - 2000 E. Broad Street - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:309)
  - New Light Baptist (old Trinity Methodist) - 2000 E. Broad Street - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:310)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - exterior (Othertype 1:311)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - interior - (Othertype 1:312)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - Creation of Earth - stained glass - (Othertype 1:313)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - Holy Spirit descending on Earth - stained glass - (Othertype 1:314)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - Got rid of snakes - stained glass - (Othertype 1:315)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - Jesus, Mary and Joseph - stained glass - (Othertype 1:316)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Parish - 213 N. 25th Street - Sisters of Charity - stained glass - (Othertype 1:317)
  - Baptist Church - 1101 Bainbridge Street - last service - (Othertype 1:318)
  - Baptist Church - 1101 Bainbridge Street - altar - (Othertype 1:319)
  - Baptist Church - 1101 Bainbridge Street - stained glass - (Othertype 1:320)
  - Baptist Church - 1101 Bainbridge Street - dedication marker - (Othertype 1:321)
  - Sixth Mt. Zion Baptist - 14 W. Duval - (Othertype 1:322)
  - Sixth Mt. Zion Baptist - 14 W. Duval - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:323)
  - Sixth Mt. Zion Baptist - 14 W. Duval - detail of pew - (Othertype 1:324)
  - First African Baptist - South side - older building - (Othertype 1:325)
  - Pine Street Baptist - 400 S. Pine and Albemarle Street - (Othertype 1:326)
  - Confederate Memorial Chapel -2900 Grove Avenue (behind Virginia Museum of Fine Arts) - (Othertype 1:327)
  - Confederate Memorial Chapel -2900 Grove Avenue - stained glass - (Othertype 1:328)
  - Confederate Memorial Chapel -2900 Grove Avenue - stained glass - (Othertype 1:329)
  - Confederate Memorial Chapel -2900 Grove Avenue - stained glass - (Othertype 1:330)
  - Sharon Baptist Church - 22 E. Leigh Street - (Othertype 1:331)
  - Sharon Baptist Church - 22 E. Leigh Street - interior - (Othertype 1:332)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - (Othertype 1:333)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - detail of vaulted ceiling - (Othertype 1:334)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - altar and stained glass - (Othertype 1:335)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - stained glass and icon paintings - (Othertype 1:336)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - icon painting - (Othertype 1:337)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - icon painting - (Othertype 1:338)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - stained glass and icon paintings - (Othertype 1:339)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - icon painting - (Othertype 1:340)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - stained glass and icon paintings - (Othertype 1:341)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - stained glass - (Othertype 1:342)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal - stained glass - (Othertype 1:343)
  - First Baptist Church - 2709 Monument Avenue - (Othertype 1:344)
  - First Baptist Church - 2709 Monument Avenue - (Othertype 1:345)
  - First Baptist Church - 2709 Monument Avenue - altar - (Othertype 1:346)
  - First Baptist Church - 2709 Monument Avenue - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:347)
  - Grace Covenant Presbyterian - 1627 Monument Avenue - exterior - (Othertype 1:348)
  - Grace Covenant Presbyterian - 1627 Monument Avenue - interior - (Othertype 1:349)
  - St. Stephens Episcopal - 6000 Grove Avenue - exterior - (Othertype 1:350)
  - St. Stephens Episcopal - 6000 Grove Avenue - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:351)
  - St. Benedict Church - 300 N. Shepard - front entrance with sculpture and rossette window - (Othertype 1:352)
  - St. Benedict Church - 300 N. Shepard -detail of entrance sculpture and rosettewindow - (Othertype 1:353)
  - St. Benedict Church - 300 N. Shepard - interior altar and apse (Othertype 1:354)
  - First Christian Science Church - 2001 Monument - (Othertype 1:355)
  - First Christian Science Church - 2001 Monument - interior - (Othertype 1:356)
  - First Christian Science Church - 2001 Monument - chairs and window - (Othertype 1:357)
  - Temple Beth El - 3332 Grove Avenue - (Othertype 1:358)
  - Temple Beth El - 3332 Grove Avenue -interior - (Othertype 1:359)
  - Temple Beth El - 3332 Grove Avenue -interior stained glass - (Othertype 1:360)
  - Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Cathedral - 30 Malvern Avenue - exterior - (Othertype 1:361)
  - Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Cathedral - 30 Malvern Avenue - interior Iconistasis from narthex - (Othertype 1:362)
  - Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Cathedral - 30 Malvern Avenue - interior icons - (Othertype 1:363)
  - Saints Constantine and Helen - Greek Orthodox Cathedral - 30 Malvern Avenue - interior icons - (Othertype 1:364)
  - Saints Constantine and Helen - Greek Orthodox Cathedral - 30 Malvern Avenue - during service - (Othertype 1:365)
- Series V: Virginia Diners., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  Virginia Diners document casual eating establishments which are specifically named or bear the characteristics of diners. Some of those shared characteristics are: being open twenty-four hours or late in the evening, offering a constant breakfast menu, or being a factory built restaurant structure transported to a site either complete or in sections with a counter. Most of the diners recorded by Calos have been in business for fifty or more years. Taken during the period of 1996 to 2005, they exhibit these traits by degrees, some reflecting the pure form and others in name only.
  The theme for Virginia Diners was inspired by The Coney Island Lunch, a cafe diner begun by his father in 1919 in Danville, Virginia. The cafe continued as a family business until December 31, 1971. The cafe became a victim of urban renewal after 52 years of service.
  This series records family run eateries across the state during the period of 1996 to 2005. Calos has carefully recorded the characteristic architecture, the interior decor, restaurant fixtures, menus, advertisements, cuisine, as well as portraits of original owners and staff.
  - East Shore Diner - Harrisburg, PA - Breakfast Plate Special - (Othertype 1:366)
  - East Shore Diner - Harrisburg, PA - Here's Looking at You (eggs and bacon) - (Othertype 1:367)
  - Coney Island Diner, Danville (copy photo)- Employees (left to right); Jim, Staffy, Cliff [Vedsley], Pol, Pete, Tony, Harold Bateman - (Othertype 1:368)
  - Chesterfield Diner - Hull Street, Richmond - staff and patrons - (Othertype 1:369)
  - Tub o' Chicken ad - Gloucester County - (Othertype 1:370)
  - Chesterfield Diner - Hull Street, Richmond - 1955 Pinball Machine - (Othertype 1:371)
  - River City Diner - 1712 E. Main, Richmond - (Othertype 1:372)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - exterior - (Othertype 1:373)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - exterior clock - (Othertype 1:374)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - aluminum exterior - (Othertype 1:375)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - maker plate, Silk City - (Othertype 1:376)
  - Exmore Diner- Northhampton County - interior - (Othertype 1:377)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - interior bar stools - (Othertype 1:378)
  - Exmore Diner - Northhampton County - table with food - (Othertype 1:379)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - street view - (Othertype 1:380)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - exterior and sign - (Othertype 1:381)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - cone machine and sign - (Othertype 1:382)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - cone machine and sign - (Othertype 1:383)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - Albert Doumar - (Othertype 1:384)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - waffle cone iron - (Othertype 1:385)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - store cones in barrel - (Othertype 1:386)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - cones in barrel - (Othertype 1:387)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - detail of cone with stamp - (Othertype 1:388)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - waitresses; Thelma and unknown female - (Othertype 1:389)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - counter - (Othertype 1:390)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - Bar-b-q lunch - (Othertype 1:391)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - drive-in - (Othertype 1:392)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - drive-in counter - (Othertype 1:393)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - Sundaes - Lab#07_1354_01 - (Othertype 1:394)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - car tray - (Othertype 1:395)
  - Doumar's - Monticello Ave, Norfolk - Albert Doumar, owner - (Othertype 1:396)
  - Blue Star Diner - Newport News - exterior - (Othertype 1:397)
  - Blue Star Diner - Newport News - maker plate; Manno - (Othertype 1:398)
  - Blue Star Diner - Newport News - Fannie [Blentson], owner since 1961 - (Othertype 1:399)
  - Blue Star Diner - Newport News - interior counter - (Othertype 1:400)
  - Wakefield - Water Tower - (Othertype 1:401)
  - Virginia Diner - Wakefield - exterior - (Othertype 1:402)
  - Virginia Diner - Wakefield - exterior sign - (Othertype 1:403)
  - Virginia Diner - Wakefield - exterior - (Othertype 1:404)
  - Virginia Diner - Wakefield - interior - (Othertype 1:405)
  - Governor Clean Award Sign - Hopewell - (Othertype 1:406)
  - Quick Lunch Diner - Hopewell - exterior - (Othertype 1:407)
  - Quick Lunch Diner - Hopewell - mounted fish sign - (Othertype 1:408)
  - Quick Lunch Diner - Hopewell - Liver and Onions - (Othertype 1:409)
  - Quick Lunch Diner - Hopewell - counter - (Othertype 1:410)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - exterior - (Othertype 1:411)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - Owners; Sally and Dick - (Othertype 1:412)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - stove and counter - (Othertype 1:413)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - stools and counter - (Othertype 1:414)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - counter and mirror - (Othertype 1:415)
  - Little Diner - Hopewell - Dr. Pepper sign, Calos reflected in mirror - (Othertype 1:416)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - exterior (Othertype 1:417)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - street view - (Othertype 1:418)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - sign logo - (Othertype 1:419)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - interior - (Othertype 1:420)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - counter and stools - (Othertype 1:421)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - interior - (Othertype 1:422)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - car bumper in wall - (Othertype 1:423)
  - River City Diner - 1712 East Main Street, Richmond - menu board - (Othertype 1:424)
  - Skull & Bones - East Broad and 14th, Richmond - downtown - (Othertype 1:425)
  - Skull & Bones - East Broad and 14th, Richmond - (Othertype 1:426)
  - Skull & Bones - East Broad and 14th, Richmond - interior - (Othertype 1:427)
  - View of downtown Richmond - corner of 1300 E. Cary - (Othertype 1:428)
  - View of mural commemorating Statute for Religious Freedom mural and Enrico Banducci Brothers Hot Dog stand - 1300 E. Cary, Richmond - (Othertype 1:429)
  - Enrico Banducci Brothers Hot Dog stand - 1300 E. Cary, Richmond - hot dog - (Othertype 1:430)
  - Enrico Banducci Brothers Hot Dog stand - 1300 E. Cary, Richmond - Owner; Enrico Banducci - (Othertype 1:431)
  - Enrico Banducci Brothers Hot Dog stand - 1300 E. Cary, Richmond - Chicago Beef Wiener - (Othertype 1:432)
  - Enrico Banducci Brothers Hot Dog stand - 1300 E. Cary, Richmond - Owner; Enrico Banducci - (Othertype 1:433)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - street view (Othertype 1:434)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - interior - (Othertype 1:435)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - stools and checkered floor - (Othertype 1:436)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - interior - (Othertype 1:437)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - Coca-Cola sign - (Othertype 1:438)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - patron in booth reading paper (Othertype 1:439)
  - 3rd Street Diner - Corner of 3rd & Main, Richmond - breakfast plate - (Othertype 1:440)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - exterior - (Othertype 1:441)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - exterior - (Othertype 1:442)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - tavern kitchen - (Othertype 1:443)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - dining room table - (Othertype 1:444)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - dining room - (Othertype 1:445)
  - Lancaster Tavern - Lancaster County - chicken dinner - (Othertype 1:446)
  - Colonial Beach Hunan Diner - Westmoreland County - exterior - (Othertype 1:447)
  - Colonial Beach Hunan Diner - Westmoreland County - exterior - (Othertype 1:448)
  - Colonial Beach Hunan Diner - Westmoreland County - prior owner Bob Mooz, Ginny Babbich, and [Paulette] - (Othertype 1:449)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - exterior - (Othertype 1:450)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - historic landmark sign - (Othertype 1:451)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - exterior sign - (Othertype 1:452)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - exterior - (Othertype 1:453)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - aluminum exterior - (Othertype 1:454)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - interior counter - (Othertype 1:455)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - interior - (Othertype 1:456)
  - Tasteee 29 Diner - Rt. 50 Fairfax - meat loaf special - (Othertype 1:457)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - exterior showing Diner sign - (Othertype 1:458)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - exterior - (Othertype 1:459)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - maker plate; Jerry Mahoney Company - (Othertype 1:460)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - interior with patrons - (Othertype 1:461)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - aluminum kitchen - (Othertype 1:462)
  - Frost Diner - Rt. 15 Warrenton - grill and counter - (Othertype 1:463)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal -exterior - (Othertype 1:464)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal - exterior sign - (Othertype 1:465)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal - aluminum exterior corner - (Othertype 1:466)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal - Owner; Sandy Williams - (Othertype 1:467)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal - interior aluminum ceiling - (Othertype 1:468)
  - Sandy's Diner - Front Royal - interior counter and stool - (Othertype 1:469)
  - Fox Diner - Front Royal - exterior - (Othertype 1:470)
  - Fox Diner - Front Royal - detail of sign - (Othertype 1:471)
  - Fox Diner - Front Royal - interior counter - (Othertype 1:472)
  - Fox Diner - Front Royal - interior counter, floor - (Othertype 1:473)
  - Valley Diner - Tom's Brook, Rt. 11 - exterior sign (Othertype 1:474)
  - Valley Diner - Tom's Brook, Rt. 11 - exterior - (Othertype 1:475)
  - L & S Diner - Liberty Street, Harrisonburg - exterior - (Othertype 1:476)
  - L & S Diner - Liberty Street, Harrisonburg - exterior - (Othertype 1:477)
  - L & S Diner - Liberty Street, Harrisonburg - sign - (Othertype 1:478)
  - L & S Diner - Liberty Street, Harrisonburg - interior with patrons - (Othertype 1:479)